{
    "subject": "resource/Dynasty_(As_They_Sleep_album)",
    "predicate": "property/released",
    "object": "2010-11-23",
    "human_readable": "The album Dynasty was released on November 23, 2010.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9278655648231506,
            "question": "Name the album released on November 23, 2010."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9215688109397888,
            "question": "Which album has a release date of November 23, 2010?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896051049232483,
            "question": "When was the album Dynasty released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8820964694023132,
            "question": "What is the name of the album that was released on November 23, 2010?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8816542029380798,
            "question": "November 23rd, 2010, saw the release of which album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8642266988754272,
            "question": "In what year was the album Dynasty released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678420305252075,
            "question": "If an album was released on November 23, 2010, what is its name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6041474938392639,
            "question": "What musical release occurred on November 23rd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5920100212097168,
            "question": "What musical work was launched on November 23rd, 2010?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5365614891052246,
            "question": "On what date did Dynasty come out?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The album Dynasty was released on November 23, 2010.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1714_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical work was launched on November 23rd, 2010?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1714_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical release occurred on November 23rd?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1714_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If an album was released on November 23, 2010, what is its name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1714_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1714_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text states that *Dynasty* was released on May 23, 1979, not November 23, 2010. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, the album \"Dynasty\" by Kiss was released on May 23, 1979, not November 23, 2010. Therefore, the statement \"The album Dynasty was released on November 23, 2010\" is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Dynasty was released on May 23, 1979, not November 23, 2010.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information provided states Dynasty was released on May 23, 1979.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The provided context information specifies the release date of the album \"Dynasty\" as May 23, 1979, not November 23, 2010.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Dynasty is the seventh studio album by Kiss, released on May 23, 1979. There is no mention of a release date in November 2010.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}